(Leonard:)It'll look so nice
next to the ones he's got...
(Leonard:)...from Leonard Nimoy,
Carl Sagan and Stan Lee.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, do you recall when I said
that I was going...
...to revolutionize understanding
of the Higgs boson particle...
...and you said, "Sheldon, it's 2 a.m.
Get out of my bedroom"?
Like it was 10 hours ago.
What about it?
Well, I believe l've done it.
I'm only saying "believe"
to sound modest...
(Sheldon:)...because, sweet Sam Houston,
l did it.
- Really?
- That's incredible. Oh, here.
(Raj:)- Break out the math.
- Oh, okay. Let me see this.
(Sheldon:)All right, so this particle here
is the boson moving forward in time.
(Sheldon:)Now, I was thinking...
(Sheldon:)Howard, you go ahead and eat.
This isn't gonna make any sense to you.
(Howard:)Sheldon, I have a working understanding
of physics.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, good for you.
And don't stop working on it.
(Raj:)You still going to tell him...
(Raj:)- ...about you-know-who?
- Yep.
- Still gonna introduce him?
- Not on your life.